[{"answer": "My God, General it", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What exactly am I looking at", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "U", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "And do we know where theyre going", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "To Teal'c, Did anything like this ever happen to you before", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Do we have a homing device", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "We have the element of surprise, I have my staff weapon. If we eliminate his personal guard quickly, I believe so", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I am okay", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh, I don't think this is Heaven", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Wasn't I just", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Killed as in", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Killed as in", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Dead", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "So there are others", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Right...we'll go", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yeah, I bet it would", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't want to", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Why do you want to fight them", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Then don't", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Mmm. You", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "We get life from the forest, from everything", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "that place, kree", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Then find me Teal'c", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Before you kill me? You're too much of a coward or you would've done it already", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You may wish you had", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "my friend'l has been this way", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-The-Nox.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "He is very skilled at evading capture", "qsentId": 30}]